const STORE = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: "Also known as the 360, this soccer move uses a spin to create separation from defenders and win yourself some extra time and space.",
      options: [
        "The Okocha", "The Roulette", "The Rabona", "The Rainbow"
      ],
      explanation: "With the ball running in front of you and the opposition player close to putting in a tackle, put your inside foot on top of the ball and roll it back slightly. At the same time, spin your body and roll the ball with your outside foot into the direction you’re turning towards. If done correctly, the ball should now be in your path as you sprint by the defender.",
      answer: "The Roulette",
    },
    {
      question: "You want to hit the ball with the outside of your foot before immediately changing direction by striking the ball with the inside of your foot and bringing the ball across your body.",
      options: [
        "The Elastico", "The Dummy", "The Fake Pull Back", "The Hocus Pocus"
      ],
      explanation: "To pull off this soccer move successfully, you want to hit the ball with the outside of your foot before immediately changing direction by striking the ball with the inside of your foot and bringing the ball across your body. Though it can be done from a stationary position, it is a lot more effective at speed. The goal is to make the defender believe you’re going one way when you’re actually going to cross the ball over and go the other direction.",
      answer: "The Elastico",
    },
    {
      question: "Show the ball to your opponent and open your body up looking like you’re able to attempt a move to blow past the defender, but instead hook the ball with the interior of your foot and slow it down.",
      options: [
        "The Rivelio", "The Nutmeg", "The Inside Hook", "The Aurelio"
      ],
      explanation: "To use it, show the ball to your opponent and open your body up looking like you’re able to attempt a move to blow past the defender, but instead hook the ball with the interior of your foot and slow it down. This drag move will give you time and space to make another move directly after, switch the play, or pass back to a teammate. Completing this move successfully requires a high level of ball control and patience.",
      answer: "The Inside Hook",
    },
    {
      question: "You prepare to receive the ball, but let it go through your legs at the last moment to another teammate.",
      options: [
        "The Shoulder Feint", "The Dummy", "The Cut", "The Hocus Pocus"
      ],
      explanation: "It starts with a pass that looks like it is going to a certain player, but that player fakes receiving or kicking the ball and then, without touching it, lets the ball continue directly past him to a teammate.",
      answer: "The Dummy",
    },
    {
      question: "While sprinting along the flank and when an opposition defender is sprinting alongside you, strike the ball with the inside of your foot and cut it behind your standing leg.",
      options: [
        "The Rainbow", "The Roulette", "The Ronaldo Chop", "The Matthews Cut"
      ],
      explanation: "While sprinting along the flank and when an opposition defender is sprinting alongside you, strike the ball with the inside of your foot and cut it behind your standing leg. The ball should end up on the opposite side from where you kicked it and both feet should rise of the ground as you make contact with the ball. To stop this move, defenders may be forced to bring the dribbler down otherwise they’ll have a free run at the goal.",
      answer: "The Ronaldo Chop",
    },
    {
      question: "With both feet on either side of the ball, use one leg to roll the ball up the back of your other leg before flicking the ball up and over the head of your opponent.",
      options: [
        "The Around the World", "The Rabona", "The Hocus Pocus", "The Rainbow"
      ],
      explanation: "With both feet on either side of the ball, use one leg to roll the ball up the back of your other leg before flicking the ball up and over the head of your opponent. If this is move you want to use, make sure to practice from a standing position before attempting to do this while on the move. While most of the soccer moves mentioned on this list are useful for game situations, you should probably keep the Rainbow locked safely away for when you’re mucking around with friends.",
      answer: "The Rainbow",
    },
    {
      question: "When facing two defenders, hold the ball between both feet and hop through the air, carrying the ball past your opposition.",
      options: [
        "The Double Lunge", "The Pull Back", "The Seal Dribble", "The La Cuauhteminha"
      ],
      explanation: "Rarely ever seen and used by predominantly by one man, \'La Cuauhteminha\' is used by Mexican football Cuauhtemoc Blanco. Often when facing two defenders, Blanco would hold the ball between both feet and hop through the air, carrying the ball past his opposition. Though not always successful, the move is highly entertaining and could leave a number of defenders embarrassed when executed properly.",
      answer: "The La Cuauhteminha",
    },
    {
      question: "Starting with the ball attached to the inside of your foot, scoop the ball behind your standing leg and then push the ball back in front to the same side of your body with the outside of the same foot.",
      options: [
        "The Hocus Pocus", "The Rabona", "The Aurelio", "The Rivelino"
      ],
      explanation: "It takes a lot of skill and ball mastery to pull off, but you’ll certainly leave your defender in a twist if you’re able to master it. Starting with the ball attached to the inside of your foot, scoop the ball behind your standing leg and then push the ball back in front to the same side of your body with the outside of the same foot. Hopefully you’ll tie your defender up in a knot instead of yourself. As usual, the quicker you’re able to do this, the better chance you’ll have of successfully pulling off the move and blowing past your defender.",
      answer: "The Hocus Pocus",
    },
    {
      question: "Place your foot on top of the ball and drag it back towards you as the defender reaches in to knock the ball away.",
      options: [
        "The Double Lunge", "The Pullback V", "The Cut", "The Elastico"
      ],
      explanation: "A pullback is executed by placing the bottom of the foot on the ball, rolling it (or flicking it) backward, and turning with it. It is a way to quickly reverse direction.",
      answer: "The Pullback V",
    },
    {
      question: "Once you’ve sold your defender a couple of dummies and they’re retreating flat-footed and unsure of what to do, slip the ball through their legs for the ultimate humiliation.",
      options: [
        "The Okocha", "The Rainbow", "The Nutmeg", "The Around the World"
      ],
      explanation: "With the huge range of soccer tricks that you can use, you’ll soon be leaving your defenders knot-legged and twisted all over the pitch. That’s when opportunities to use the nutmeg will arise. Once you’ve sold your defender a couple of dummies and they’re retreating flat-footed and unsure of what to do, slip the ball through their legs for the ultimate humiliation. Then quickly slip past them and gain possession of the ball again. No player likes to be nutmegged and I guarantee it’ll be on their minds for the rest of the match. They’ll think twice before trying to tackle you again.",
      answer: "The Nutmeg",
    },
  ],
  currentQuestion: 0,
  currentScore: 0,
  scores: []
};